

PROFILE

I am an aspiring Data Analyst having 3+ years of experience in IT industry.

I started my career in Tech Mahindra as a Technical Support Analyst and worked on SAP ERP. Worked on Excel & PowerPoint for making reports and presentations. Worked on Microsoft Word for making SOPs. Worked on my communication skills such as Volume & Clarity, Empathy, Active listening, Friendliness, Giving & receiving feedback & Email Writing as interacting with International client on daily basis. Get flexible in 24*7 Shift timings.

After that I worked on Salesforce, Excel Reports and Presentations. I was focused more on Email Writing as I was interacting with Brand Mercedes- Benz Customers.

Currently, I am working as a Data Analyst & Experienced in

- Cleaning and preparing data for analysis.
- Perform Basic Visualization on given data and can make reports & presentations.
- Performing Testing before migration of tool on Production.
- Experienced in Giving Skype trainings on internal tools among the organization.

MONIKA PARASHAR

Data Analyst | Data Modeling | Data Warehousing | Data Mining | SQL | Power Point | Tech Support

EDUCATION

Vidya College of Engineering, Meerut (U.P)-India B.Tech (Electrical and Electronics Engineering) 2011-2015 (68%)

K.V.Sikh Lines, Meerut (U.P)-India Intermediate College - 2010-2011 (70%) (PCM)

K.V.Sikh Lines, Meerut (U.P)-India High School - 2009– 2010 (74%)

WORK EXPERIENCE

$Team\ Lease\ (Client\ -\ Schneider\ Electric) - Data\ Analyst$

May 2019 - Apr 2020

- Collecting data and standardizing according to client's requirements.
- Transforming data using data management tools and techniques (Such as Tableau, MS Excel)
- Collaborating operational support for the coordination and execution of data governance activities, drive continuous improvement, manage noncompliance issue escalations, and provide training through Skype and communication to Countries.
- Working on ticketing tool BMC and JIRA
- Well versed with **Data wrangling** using **MSVS & SSDT-BI**.

Allianz Partners - Analyst (Excel | Power Point)

June 2018 - April 2019

- Worked with the leading luxury segment vehicle manufacturer as a part of CRM Team.
- End to end management of complaints registered with the company by way of social media, toll free helpline and email portal.
- Supervision of dealerships across India.
- Client handling by way submission of reports of daily, weekly & monthly operations including TAT's actions and actionable etc.

CERTIFICATIONS

Udemy - Data Science

CONTACT

PHONE:

+91-9205255808

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/monika-parashar-2523b4a1

EMAIL:

Parashar.monika15@gmail.com

DOB: 09/12/1993

Creating accounts, managing accounts by adding comments/activities/attachments for new customers/existing customers on Salesforce.

Achievements:

Achieved "STAR OF THE MONTH" in Complaint Management for the month of December by Mercedes-Benz India within the short span of time.

Sharika Enterprises- Analyst

October 2017- Jan 2018

- Coordinating with the team by managing schedules, filing important documents and communicating relevant information regarding ongoing and upcoming projects.
- Managing and coordinating complete cycle of Project including Project Initialization, Planning, Execution, Monitoring, and Controlling and Closing etc. on Excel for making reports.
- > Supporting Tendering and Finance Team for project documents during the time for bidding.
- Attend Meetings for building Customer relationship and to grab more business opportunities.

Tech Mahindra- Tech Support Analyst

May 2016 - September 2017

- Worked as a System Admin (Windows Active Directory).
- Provide Authorization to Dannon users in SAP ERPTool.
- Providing support to the active as well as retired employees of American Airlines.
- Providing mobility support for their company provided devices like IPhone, Mac book etc. thereby trouble shooting the errors further explaining the various procedures.
- Escalate cases under **Service Now** and create Incident number.
- Navigate employees to request for conference room, increase mailbox size, new email account, permissions for access of shared mailbox etc. through SharePoint.

Achievements:

Got calls and mails of appreciations from clients.

Achieved "BRAVO" and "SPOT" at Rewards and Recognition within the short span of time.

SKILLS

Excel – VLOOKUP, CHARTS, Math formulas, TRIM, CONCATENATE, VBA (Basics) etc.

Tableau – Data Visualization, Data Mining, Chi-square test, bins, calculated field,

SOL - Basics

MSVS - SSIS